// Creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "How is the Web different from the Internet?",
    answer: "A. The internet involves larger networks than the web.",
    options: [
      "A. The internet involves larger networks than the web.",
      "B. The web is software while the internet is the hardware.",
      "C. The internet is an older term people used for the web.",
      "D. There is no difference between the two."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which device is NOT included in ICT?",
    answer: "D. Twitter.",
    options: [
      "A. Smartphone.",
      "B. Internet.",
      "C. Wrist Watch",
      "D. Twitter."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Reddit is an online platform where people can create a post (subreddit) and other people can respond to it. Which web version is characterized by Reddit?",
    answer: "B. Web 2.0",
    options: [
      "A. Web 1.0",
      "B. Web 2.0",
      "C. Web 3.0",
      "D. Reddit is not a website"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "How will you describe if something is ICT?",
    answer: "D. These are hardware or software that allows access, storage, transmission, and manipulation of information.",
    options: [
      "A. ICT focuses on the hardware aspect of networks where it allows interconnection of networks.",
      "B. ICT refers to systems and protocols used inside the internet to enable other computers to interact with other computers.",
      "C. These are new technologies that allow people to communicate quickly with each other.",
      "D. These are hardware or software that allows access, storage, transmission, and manipulation of information."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which ICT trend is described with the statement above?",
    answer: "C. Mobile Technologies",
    options: [
      "A. Convergent Technologies",
      "B. Social Media",
      "C. Mobile Technologies",
      "D. World Wide Web"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following website functionalities demonstrates web 2.0 capability?",
    answer: "C. Leaving a like on a picture on a social media site.",
    options: [
      "A. An author making an article for people to read.",
      "B. Posting details of an item for sale online.",
      "C. Leaving a like on a picture on a social media site.",
      "D. Reverse searching the web for an image."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What does ICT stand for?",
    answer: "A. Information and Communication Technology.",
    options: [
      "A. Information and Communication Technology.",
      "B. Integral Convergent Technology",
      "C. Interoperable Cellular Telecommunication",
      "D. Information Communication Technology"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "How will you describe Social Media?",
    answer: "B. These are platforms that allow users to communicate in online social communities.",
    options: [
      "A. Multiple different devices combine into a single gadget because of technological advancement.",
      "B. These are platforms that allow users to communicate in online social communities.",
      "C. This is the miniaturization of previously heavy or big technology.",
      "D. These are web technologies that allow the user to add content."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which best describes the Web 3.0 keyword “Executable”?",
    answer: "C. Processing the input of the user based on other data.",
    options: [
      "A. This is the interaction of different applications on your device.",
      "B. The use of mobile applications interacting with other applications.",
      "C. Processing the input of the user based on other data.",
      "D. The Keyword of Web 3.0 is not Executable."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the difference between all the web technologies (web 1.0, web 2.0, and web 3.0)?",
    answer: "D. Functionality and features that it represents.",
    options: [
      "A. Web technological milestones as invented at certain time periods.",
      "B. It represents the computer hardware technology the web is running on.",
      "C. These are different versions of the web protocols that run on the internet.",
      "D. Functionality and features that it represents."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "What is HTTP?",
    answer: "A. It is the Hyper Text Transfer Protocol or the very code a website uses to be displayed.",
    options: [
      "A. It is the Hyper Text Transfer Protocol or the very code a website uses to be displayed.",
      "B. It acts as a web program that analyzes data transfers for malicious codes.",
      "C. It is the procedure of how data is transferred online between different networks.",
      "D. It is a markup language that details how different elements are displayed."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "As a Technological Trend, why are smartphones an example of mobile technology?",
    answer: "D. It is a device that utilizes cellular communication technology.",
    options: [
      "A. It is the combination of different technological devices.",
      "B. It is an example of a device that is small and portable.",
      "C. It allows instant mass communication.",
      "D. It is a device that utilizes cellular communication technology."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Which is the best example of the current technology that demonstrates full Web 3.0 technology?",
    answer: "D. Web 3.0 is not yet fully realized or developed.",
    options: [
      "A. E-commerce sites like Lazada or Shopee.",
      "B. Self-correcting spelling functions in Microsoft applications.",
      "C. Smartphone applications.",
      "D. Web 3.0 is not yet fully realized or developed."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Which ICT technological trend is described in the given statement?",
    answer: "C. Convergent Technologies",
    options: [
      "A. Social Media",
      "B. Mobile Technologies",
      "C. Convergent Technologies",
      "D. Cellular Communication"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "What definition describes the Internet?",
    answer: "A. It is the interconnection of computers, hardware, and networks.",
    options: [
      "A. It is the interconnection of computers, hardware, and networks.",
      "B. It allows the transfer of data from one computer to another.",
      "C. It is a network of different web applications that allow quick transfer of data.",
      "D. It is the collection of different websites and webpages searchable using web browsers."
    ]
  },
];
